iqtell.com 2016-12-03

# Privacy Policy

Version Date: April 14, 2015

### Introduction

This privacy policy applies to http://www.iqtell.com owned and operated by IQTELL.COM, LLC. This privacy policy describes how IQTELL.COM, LLC collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web site: http://www.iqtell.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

IQTELL.COM, LLC (“IQTELL”) takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. We are committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity and security of personal information about our current and prospective users. This Privacy Policy explains how we protect your personal information and use this protection to service your account. By using IQTELL, you agree to the terms set forth in this privacy policy.

IQTELL.COM, LLC has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe’s program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html "TRUSTe Program Requirements") including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at privacy.policy@iqtell.com. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request "Contact TRUSTe"). The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site: [iqtell.com](http://iqtell.com/ "IQTELL"), and does not cover information that may be collected through our mobile application.

### Information Collection & Use

IQTELL collects personal information when you register with IQTELL, when you use IQTELL products or services, when you visit IQTELL pages. When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, and financial information such as credit card number and expiration date. When you register with IQTELL and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. IQTELL collects personal information about your transactions with us.

You may also provide personal information about other people, such as their email address. This information is only used for the sole purpose of completing your request or for whatever reason it may have been provided.

The contents of your IQTELL account are stored and maintained on IQTELL servers in order to provide the service. Because we keep back-up copies of data for the purposes of recovery from errors or system failure, residual copies of any account information may remain on our systems for some time, even after you have deleted information or after the termination of your account. IQTELL employees do not access the content of account information unless you specifically request them to do so (for example, if you are having technical difficulties accessing your account) or if required by law, to maintain our system, or to protect IQTELL or the public.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

We also may collect information about the use of your account, such as how much storage you are using, how often you log in and other information related to your registration and use of IQTELL. Information displayed or clicked on in your IQTELL account (including UI elements, IQTELL user interface.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

IQTELL will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. IQTELL does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * To clarify, if required by law, it may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of IQTELL’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

We transfer information about you if IQTELL is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, IQTELL will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

### Access to Personal Information

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete/deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at privacy.policy@iqtell.com. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

### Children

IQTELL is intended for a general audience, and children under the age of thirteen are not permitted to register with IQTELL. If any of IQTELL’s affiliated providers offers a site directed toward children, or knowingly collects information from children, that affiliated provider is required to provide you information about its practices for the handling of children’s online data through its privacy policy.

### Tracking Technologies

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by IQTELL.COM, LLC, affiliates, analytics or customer service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. We use cookies for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

### Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

### Log Files

As is true of most web sites, IQTELL automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser and store it in log files, including your IP address, IQTELL cookie information, software and hardware attributes, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data and the page you request. We do not link this automatically collected data to personal information. IQTELL uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

### Local Storage Objects (Flash/HTML5)

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 or Flash to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please click [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html).

### Testimonal

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [support@iqtell.com](mailto:support@iqtell.com).

### Public Forums

Public content includes any information you submit to IQTELL outside of your secured account. For example, you may voluntarily provide information about yourself when you participate in, message boards, blogs, or other community features that are accessible by general visitors and other users. This information is public content because people do not need a password to access or view this content on our site. This public content (including photographs and videos) that you choose to post outside of your secured account is not private.

To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at privacy.policy@iqtell.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

### Links to Other Websites

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by IQTELL. Please be aware that we, IQTELL, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy policy of each and every Web site that collects personal information.

This privacy policy applies only to information collected by this Web site.

### Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Facebook social plugin or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Import Contacts

You can import contacts from other email account address books to use within the service or invite them to become members of our site. When importing contacts from a supported provider, we collect the username and password for the email account you wish to import your contacts from and will only use it for that purpose.

### Single Sign-On

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect, Google OpenID Connect, Twitter sign-in, or Yahoo OAuth. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

### Confidentiality and Security

IQTELL stores its servers in a highly secure server environment with 24/7 monitoring, surveillance and support to prevent unauthorized access and data security. Advanced security measures including firewalls, security guards and surveillance are taken to ensure the continued service and protection of your data from natural disaster, intruders and disruptive events. The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer (SSL) technology. We cannot guarantee the security of your data while it is being transmitted over the Internet and through servers that are out of our control. We strive to protect your personal information but IQTELL cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to our website or services. Any data transmissions you make over the internet are done so at your own risk. Once we receive the data transmission, we make our best efforts to ensure its security and privacy on our systems.

### Policy Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and notify our users, so that our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it prior to the change becoming effective. We will always use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please email us at [privacy.policy@iqtell.com](mailto:privacy.policy@iqtell.com) or contact us via postal mail at 2477 Route 516, Old Bridge, NJ 08857.

﻿
